(Howard:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)I'm just distracted by something
that happened over at Penny's.
(Amy:)What happened?
(Sheldon:)I fear Penny is being unfaithful
to Leonard.
(Penny:)-What?
-She claimed to be alone
(Sheldon:)when there was obviously
someone else in her apartment.
(Sheldon:)I have no choice but
to assume the worst,
(Sheldon:)given Leonard's lengthy sea voyage
(Sheldon:)and her famously
ravenous nether regions.
(Amy:)I don't think Penny
would cheat on Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)She and I once had
a staring contest.
(Sheldon:)She clapped really loud
and made me blink.
(Sheldon:)It's a small leap from there
to sexual infidelity.
(Amy:)You're being ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)Amy, there were Chinese
food containersu. in the trash can.
(Amy:)Poor Leonard.